Guide to the James Buell Munn Collection 1873-1980 MC 2 MC.2
New York University Archives
- Addendum - Series I: Acquisition
  - Alumni/Colleagues - Correspondence Includes current correspondence with respect to the acqui­ sition of extant Munn papers and memoirs written by former students and colleagues at Washington Square College., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Munn Scholarship Fund - Correspondence Correspondence include Jill Claster, Bayrd Still., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Munn Students - Printed Material (about) Includes articles about: Jacob Goldstein Murray Israel Manfred E. Lee Alfred Marrow, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Addendum - Series II: Munn Correspondence
  - Folders contain Munn correspondence received from: Melvin Albert - Nov., 1923 (copy; original in Estate Collection). H. Thomas Austern - Oct., 1927 - Nov., 1929. Alexander Baltzley - Yearly exchange of letters from Christmas 1936 to Christmas 1945; Dec. 1948 - Dec., 1957 (intermittent); Mrs. Munn, February, 1960; December, 1928, Francis J. Bloustein, 1925-1942, Benjamin and Dorothy Butner - Oct. - Nov. 1932; Nov. - Dec. 1933. Julius Evans - 1932; 1947-1948 Jacob D. Goldstein - May, 1926 Isidore S. Immerman - Jan.-Feb., 1924; June, 1926; Jan., 1947; April - May, 1959; Jan. 1962; March 1968; March, 1972; Feb., 1973; June, 1974. (Includes correspondence from Mrs. Munn). Sidney Leibowitz - Sept., 1931 - June, 1935. James L. Mandel - Aug., 1947; Nov., - Dec., 1962; March, 1960s Jacob Rabkin - Nov., 1949; July, 1951; Nov., 1952. Arthur I. Singer - July, 1943 - Nov., 1945 Hyman Lehan - Dec. 27, 1956 Irving H. Jurow - June - July, 1926; May 1971 - June 1974 Charles Norman - Aug. 1968 - Aug. 1971, 1923-1971 (Box 10)
- Addendum - Series III: Memoirs
  - Folders contain memoirs of Munn received from H. Thomas Austern - July, 1979. (Includes memorandum by B. Parnes re meeting between H.T. Austern Bayrd Still, Alexander Baltzly - Jan. 1976. Written at request of William L. Blackwell, Chairman, History Department). Margaret L. Brown - April 20, 1979 (Bayrd Still oral history interview). Benjamin Butner - see Sept 15, 1979 letter to Bayrd Still. Series I, Folder 5. Rabbi Armond E. Cohen - Jan. 25, 1982 letter to Dean Jill N. Claster, WSUC Miguel A. de Capriles - May, 1976 (Excerpts, Bayrd Still oral history interview). Jacob Fisher - 1978 (See also: Jacob Fisher, On Vanishing Ground, 1979, NYU Archives, Rz 1). John Frost - Bulletin (of NYU Libraries); article, 1964; letter, 1979. Isidore S. Immerman - Sept. 13, 1979 (Transcript of discussion with Bayrd Still). Sidney Leibowitz - June, 1979. James L. Mandel - Sept. 2, 1979 (Includes list of letters from Mandell to Munn Located in Munn Collection, Harvard University Library). Bernard Newman - Sept 14, 1979 Teresa Newman - Sept. 5, 1979 Charles Norman - See: Charles Norman, The Well of the Past, 1949. NYU Archives, Rz 2; Poets and People, 1972, NYU Archives, Rz 3. Leon Pomerance - Sept. 1, 1979 George Saslow - July, 1979 Hilda G. Schwartz - Sept. 20, 1979 William R. Taylor - May 27, 1980., 1976-1982 (Box 10)
- Addendum - Series IV: Photographs
  - H. Thomas Austern - photograph of John P. and James B. Munn "receiving the Colors" at New York University, c. 1920's; Munn in 1963. Isidore Immerman - Alpha Lambda Phi dinner meeting, May 28, 1927. (see oversized box) Mrs. Bruno Lever - photograph of JBM in Washington Square College Yearbook Album, n.d., ca.1920-1963 (Box 11)
- Addendum - Series V: Publications - Munn Students
  - Murray Israel - Offprints of professional articles Charles Norman - The Well of the Past (1949).- Poets and People (1979)., 1949, 1979 (Box 11)
- Addendum - Series VI: Material derived from New York University Archives
  - Munn correspondence - New York University Administration, 1926-1932 (Box 11)
  - Photographs - Dr. J.P. Munn, Chancellor Brown, Major Marilsky on viewing Stand; November 23, 1917. See also: New York University Archives Photograph Collection Commencements (Box 11)
  - Military, undated (Box 11)
- Addendum - Series VII: James Buell Munn Exhibit (May - September, 1980)
  - Correspondence and publicity (see Bayrd Still files) Brochure, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Photographs by Paul Occhiogrosso, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Labels/Inclusions (for use in Archives exhibit case), 1980 (Box 11)
  - Munn Exhibition Brochures, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)